SIVAGANESH UI/UX DESIGNER

• Chidambaram, TamilNadu.

Career Objective

As a User Experience Designer, I love to work together with software and design firms, communicating application design principles and strategies for ongoing development. My aim is to create better interfaces and experiences for the user, making the web, application's and technology easier for the user.

Education

Bsc. Visual Communication,

Annamalai University, Chidambaram.

Aug 2017 - Dec 2020

Employment History

UX Designer [Freelancer], Contasy 11 UX Designer [Intern], Think42labs

Sep 2020 - Feb 2021 Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

Skills

Adobe Photoshop \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet Webflow \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet Adobe XD HTML & CSS \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet Bootstrap

Languages

Tamil (Native)
English (Good Working Knowledge)

Hobbies

Designing own concept apps, Redesign apps and websites, Drawing, Cricket, Music, Travel.